

Full Stack Developer P Edmonton, AB

Diverse Full Stack Developer with industry experience in federal government, education and oil & gas. Passionate, motivated to learn and driven about creating exceptional end-user experiences, I build things that live on the web.

github.com/arismink fi krisminala.netlify.app in linkedin.com/in/krismina

SKILLS

Languages: Ruby, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL, C# Systems & Databases: PostgreSQL, MySQL, Git

Tools & Technologies: Ajax, Axios, Bootstrap, Express, EJS, Heroku, jQuery, NodeJS, Rails, ReactJS

Tests: Jest, Storybook, Cypress, Mocha, Chai

PROJECTS

Herbiview • April 2022 • (live demo)

- An app that allows an individual to upload an image of plant and retrieve information about it including health assessment and toxicity towards cats, dogs and horses.
- Create an account and keep track of the plants you look up or peruse the database
- Tech-stack: React, Express, PostgreSQL, NodeJS

Scheduler April 2022 (live demo)

- Scheduling app built with React that allows users to book, modify or cancel interview appointments
- Tested with Storybook, Jest, Cypress and CircleC
- Tech-stack: React, JavaScript, PostgreSQL, NodeJS

Kool-Kids Snax (March 2022 (customer demo) (vendor demo)

- An app that uses the Twilio API to notify the vendor via SMS that an order has been placed when a customer places an order. The customer is notified via SMS when the restaurant updates the order as well as when the order is ready to be
- Designed and built the front-end of the application using HTML/CSS/SASS, EJS, JS
- Tech-stack: JavaScript, EJS, Express, NodeJS, PostgreSQL

WORK EXPERIENCE



Building Systems Security Analyst • University of Alberta

March 2021 - February 2022

- Analyze existing business systems and identify areas of opportunity for improvement in scalability
- Engage with stakeholders, developers and business users to identify and determine business requirements, and provide recommendations
- Create proposals and documentation outlining business requirements, steps of implementation, and project planning



Business Systems Analyst • Red Deer Ironworks

June 2017 - March 2021

- Organized and delivered Epicor ERP data migration and system maintenance.
- Diagnose and troubleshoot technical issues and bugs relating to the ERP system.
- Communicate with business users to understand their needs to make the necessary technical enhancements to the ERP to improve business efficiency.
- Develop and improve functional management reports using Crystal Reports and Microsoft SSRS.
- Utilize MySQL and program in C# to improve front-end data capture processes within the ERP to aid in accounting, sales and production transactions.
- Write SQL queries to capture, manipulate and produce data reports and sets as requested by users

EDUCATION



March 2022 - May 2022

Lighthouse Labs

Web Development



2012 - 2017

University of Alberta